macu.com 2011-04-28

# 

                                                                                                                 Rev 04/2011
                      WHAT DOES MOUNTAIN AMERICA CREDIT UNION DO
FACTS                 WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
                      Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
Why?                  consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how
                      we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                      understand what we do.
What?                 The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                      have with us. This information can include:
                            Name, address, Social Security Number and income
                            Credit history and credit scores
                            Account balances and transaction history
                      When you are no longer our member, we will only continue to share your information as
                      permitted or required by law as described in this notice.
How?                  All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday
                      business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’
                      personal information; the reasons Mountain America Credit Union chooses to share; and whether
                      you can limit this sharing.
                                                              Does Mountain America
Reasons we can share your personal information                                              Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                Credit Union share?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain
                                                                        Yes                              No
your account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes—
                                                                        Yes                              No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                      Yes                              No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                        Yes                              No
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                         No                       We don’t share
information about your creditworthiness
For our affiliates to market to you                                     Yes                              No
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                       No                       We don’t share
                      Call 1-800-748-4302, go to www.macu.com, or write to us at Mountain
Questions?            America Credit Union, PO Box 9001, West Jordan, UT 84084.
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?                     Mountain America Credit Union

Page 2
What we do
How does Mountain America Credit               To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
Union protect my personal information?         and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                               These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                               and buildings.
                                               Additionally, we restrict access to nonpublic personal information to our
                                               employees, employees of our affiliates, and those who need to know that
                                               information in order to provide products or services to you, to collect
                                               delinquencies, or to otherwise deal with you accounts.
How does Mountain America Credit               We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Union collect my personal information?
                                                   Open an account or deposit/withdraw money
                                                   Apply for any credit union service(s)
                                                   Pay your bills or apply for a loan
                                                   Use your credit or debit card(s)
                                                   Information from our website
                                                   Obtain a product or service from Mountain America Financial
                                                    Services, LLC or Mountain America Insurance Services, LLC
                                              We also collect personal information about you from others including credit
                                              bureaus and other companies
Why can’t I limit all sharing?                 Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                                   sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information
                                                    about your creditworthiness
                                                   affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                                   sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                               State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                               limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                                     Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                               financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                                   Mountain America Financial Services & Mountain America Insurance
                                                    Services
Nonaffiliates                                  Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                               financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                                   Mountain America Credit Union does not share with non-affiliates so
                                                    they can market to you
Joint marketing                                A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                               together market financial products or services to you.
                                                   Our joint marketing partners include investment and financial service
                                                    providers and insurance companies
Other important information
Mountain America Credit Union reserves the right to modify, change, or amend this Privacy Statement at any time
without notice other than as expressly required by applicable law. Since privacy practices may change, please check
www.macu.com regularly to view the most current version of our privacy statement. Mountain America Federal Credit
Union does business as Mountain America Credit Union.
